vpsfast.net 2018-08-15

# Privacy Policy - VPSFAST

VPSFast considers it essential to safeguard its clients identities and other personal information. We ensure that all personal information collected from our customers remains private. The following policy defines how we handle your privacy. This policy is applicable for information collected by us from you online; it does not apply to information collected offline. By using the VPSFast.us website, you are accepting this privacy policy.

### Collecting information

We save your information when you register an account, when you send us an email and when you enquire about a product or solution over the phone. This information includes your name, email address and phone number.

### Utilization

The information we collect is only used in certain circumstances. Here are a few examples of how your information may be used.

### Communication

By default, all account-related communication is sent to your email address. Technical, billing and other queries will also be responded to by email. Important announcements and newsletters (if you have subscribed) will be sent to your email address.

### Customer Relationship

From time to time, our customer relations team may get in touch with you by telephone or email. Please note that if we phone you, we will never ask you to share your credit card or bank details.

### Information Protection

VPSFast has proper tools and processes in place to ensure that your personal information is safe. In the event of an account being compromised (password sharing or malicious software installed on the user’s computers that steals information), VPSFast cannot be held responsible for any breach of security or theft of information.

### Cookies

Cookies are installed on your browsers when you access a website. They identify your browser and remember values that you’ve entered when previously visiting the site. Cookies are only used to improve your browsing experience. The information they collect is not shared with others, and you can, at any time, change your browser settings to stop cookies from sending data to us. VPSFast does not share your information with any third parties. If the need arises, we will do so only after obtaining your express permission. However, in certain instances, if governmental or regulatory bodies request information, we are bound by law to provide it.

### Changes and Updates

Parts or the whole of this privacy policy may be modified from time to time. Changes will be updated on the website without notification. We request that you check this page periodically to stay updated on our privacy policy.
